sailnet.com 2011-12-31

# SailNet Privacy Policy

**SailNet Privacy Policy**

**Summary**

SailNet Values and respects the privacy of the customers and community members. Because we gather certain types of information we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the SailNet website that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by Marine.com LLC, its partners or affiliates. These privacy practices apply only to online transactions, activity and to all email communications. 

SailNet will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all email delivery to assure your privacy. 

All credit card transactions are processed through secure connections. SailNet uses proven technologies that improve the privacy of our customers and community members information. 

When we do share information with our partners and advertisers, it is in aggregate form, and does not identify you personally. SailNet does not collect or use any information about you except for the information that you provide or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make the services provided more relevant to your interests. Under no circumstances is your email address ever shared with advertisers. SailNet provides both free services and a SailNet Store. Our SailNet Store as well as sponsors supports the free services. By becoming a SailNet customer or community member, you agree to the SailNet services agreement terms and conditions. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does SailNet.com Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at SailNet.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

Information You Give Us: We receive and may store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Websites, we use "cookies," and we may obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses SailNet.com. 

Email Communications: To help us make emails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open email from SailNet.com if your computer supports such capabilities. 

Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

**What About Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of SailNet.coms coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

**Does SailNet.com Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others at this time. Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of SailNet.com customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences. 

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that SailNet.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

Protection of SailNet.com and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with laws SailNet This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such SailNet.com features. 

If you do not want to receive email from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

**Services Agreement and terms and conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit SailNet.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Delaware. If you have any concern about privacy at SailNet.com, please send us a thorough description and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Services Agreement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes.   
  
All times are GMT -4. The time now is 04:33 PM.
